（忆往昔）
我是Henry Winchester
Henry Winchester.
我的父亲 我的祖父 都是学者
My father, his father before him were both Men of Letters.
如果你们那么厉害
If you guys were such a big deal.
为什么我们从来没听说过
Then why haven't we ever heard of you.
Josie
Josie.
没人告诉我这个入会仪式这么隆重
No one told me this initiation was a formal affair.
最艰难的时候已经过去了 对吧
The hard part's over, right.
我们挺过来了
We made it.
你对1958年
What do you know about.
学者大屠杀知道些什么
The men of letters' massacre, 1958.
我是Abaddon
My name is Abaddon.
我们大步挺进地狱
We'll march into hell.
恶魔崛起 大放光彩
And demon kind will rise up and.
横扫世界
Sweep over the earth.
谁让Crowley管事的
Who put Crowley in charge.
你们的王已经死了
The King's dead.
现在是女王万岁
Long live the Queen.
你知道该隐之印
You knew about the mark.
你知道Abaddon和Cain之间的纠葛
You knew about Abaddon and Cain.
你什么都知道
You knew all of it.
你耍我
And you played me.
你们欠我
You owe me.
你们让我变成瘾君子
You make me a junkie.
在我的王国土崩瓦解之时把我关在这儿
Keep me stashed away for months while my kingdom falls apart.
初刃在哪儿
So where's the blade.
近在眼前
This is the object of your quest.
Dean
Dean.
把初刃放下
Drop the blade.
我就先拿着这个
I'll hang on to old donkey teeth here.
等你们找到Abaddon了再说
Until such time as you locate Abaddon.
（米尔顿市 伊利诺伊州）
我非常喜欢
So I'll tell you one of the things I really love.
Tour Angle 144的一点是
About the Tour Angle 144.
很多人可能
There are a lot of you out there that.
会经常有翻倒这个问题
Have something called the chipping yips.
你们并不喜欢
You're not proud of having them.
很多人甚至连说都不想说
A lot of people don't really wanna talk about it.
如果您没碰上过这种事情 那就偷着乐吧
If you don't have them, be glad.
但是
But.
我可以告诉你们 这件产品
I got to tell you, this product.
今晚吃什么
What's on the menu tonight.
肉饼
Meat loaf.
真的吗
Really.
又吃肉饼
Again.
你真的不应该抱怨的
I wish you wouldn't say that.
你知道我每天上班多辛苦
You know how hard I work all day.
然后你还说三道四的
And yet you criticise me.
没错 我们今晚就吃肉饼
So yes, we're having meat loaf.
配土豆
With potatoes.
西兰花
And broccoli.
还有其他好吃的
And lots of good things.
嘿
Hey.
你昨晚有休息过吗
You catch any shut-eye last night.
没
No.
那就我来开车
Guess I'm driving then.
去哪儿
Driving where.
在网上无意间找到一件案子
Caught wind of a case online.
小学一年级的老师回家杀了她丈夫
First grade teacher came home and killed her husband.
也许她气过头了
Well, maybe she snapped.
小孩子有一种让人变得狂躁的能力
Ankle biters can do that to you.
她把她丈夫砸成了肉块
Dude, she pounded him into ground chunk.
那你怎么看
So, what do you take it.
我猜是被附身了
Best guess, possession.
那你怎么还不去
Why don't you go.
Dean 我也想找到Abaddon
Dean, look, I wanna find Abaddon too.
但是我们已经查了好几天了 还是一无所获
But, we've been combing through these stuffs for days.
也许漏查了
Maybe we missed something.
也许
And maybe.
比起坐在这儿 我们可以把时间
There're better ways to spend our time.
- 用在其他 - 也许我们没时间
- Than spend our - Maybe we don't have time.
你怎么了
What's up with you.
- 没事 - 是吗
- Nothing - Yeah.
自从你杀了Magnus之后
See, because ever since you killed Magnus.
你就变得有些
You've been acting…sorta.
入魔了
Obsessed.
也许是因为我想了结这一切
Well, maybe because I want an end all of this.
也许因为 如果我们找到Abaddon
Maybe because if we find Abaddon.
Crowley就会送上初刃
Then Crowley ponies up the first blade.
我们就能两个都干掉
And we kill her, end him, both.
所以 你说的入魔
So what you called being obsessed.
我说是工作
I call doing my job.
好吧
Okay.
懂了
I get it.
Dean 我就只是 看看你好不好
Dean, I'm just…checking in.
我很好
I'm fine.
好吧
All right.
发现什么了告诉我一声
Hit me up if you find anything.
你的报告里说
Says here in your report.
你是第一批到现场的
You're the first on scene.
是的
Yes, sir.
当时Young女士就坐在
Found Mrs.Young sitting next to.
她丈夫尸体旁边 全身都是血
Her husband covered in his blood.
她丈夫虐待她吗
Now, was her husband abusive.
Rick吗 不 完全不会
Rick?No, not at all.
有时候是挺混账的 但是
He could be a stubborn ass sob but.
我们谁不是呢
Can't we all.
还有其他的吗 其他你能想到的很奇怪的事
Anything else?Weird that maybe you thought.
写不进报告的那种
Was too odd to include.
- 比如什么 - 比如
- Like - Like.
硫磺的味道
Smell of sulfur.
为什么会有硫磺的味道
Why would I smell sulfur.
说的是
Of course.
谢谢
Thank you.
那Karen的眼睛呢
What about…Karen's eyes.
你有发现什么可疑之处吗
Have you noticed anything strange.
说实话 探员
Actually agent, they.
它们看上去就像是人类的眼睛
Pretty much look like eyes.
我的天
Oh, lord.
我不明白
I don't get this.
Karen和Rick是这世界上
Karen and Rick were two of most ordinary people.
最普通的普通人
You'd ever meet.
她 案发那天都去哪儿了
Did she…go anywhere on the day of the murder.
那天是周六
It was Saturday.
去了一趟杂货店 然后就没了
Quick trip to the grocery store, it's about that.
Manson太太还好吗
How is Mrs.Manson doing.
注 Charles Manson美国著名连环杀手
在上个世纪70年代领导类似人民公社的Manson Family.
在监狱里上吊死了
Dead, hung herself on the cell.
真棒
Lovely.
恶魔冒出去了吗
Demon smoke out.
不是恶魔
It wasn't a demon.
没有硫磺 EMF指数也没变
There's no sulfur, no EMF anywhere.
她杀人前 所有见过她的人都说
Anyone who saw her just before she gutted her husband.
她没有任何不正常的地方
Said she was totally fine.
那你还在那儿干什么
So what are you still doing there.
我看就是一个疯婆娘而已
Sounds like the case of craziness to me.
要是到早上没其他事 我就回去了
If nothing kicks by morning, I'm out of here.
你查的怎么样了
How's research going.
还在查
It's going.
好吧
All right, well.
好运
Good luck.
如果你真的想要
I can give you the mark, Dean.
我可以把印记给你 Dean
If it's what truly you want.
- 我能用这个杀那婊子吗 - 可以
- Can I use it to kill that bitch - Yes.
但是你得知道
But you have to know.
有了这个印记 随之而来的还有巨大的负担
With the mark comes a great burden.
嗯
Yeah.
我知道 对不起
No, I know, I'm sorry.
我会补偿你的
I'll make it up to you.Look.
宝贝儿 我正急着赶过去
I'm trying to get there, babe.
但是出来之前我跟我老妈吵了一架
I got into a fight with my mom.
我得挂了
I think I got to bye.
对 一辆小货车停下来愿意载我一程
Yeah, a van's pulling up and let me roll.
爱你 拜拜
I love you, bye.
嗨 我没发现这是你的车 Richie先生
Hi, I don't know this is your ride, Mr.Richie.
赶紧上来吧
Let's get you out of the cold.
谢谢
Thanks.
外面真是冻死了
It's freezing out there.
你 你 你 你干什么 离我远点儿
Hey, what…what…what're you doing, get off me.
圣博纳文图尔修道院
St Bonaventure.
给
Here you go.
谢谢 RJ
Thanks, RJ.
还需要什么别的吗
Can I get you anything else, honey.
不需要了 谢谢
This is great.Thank you.
待会来找你 Bill
Be with you in a minute, Bill.
Billy 你在干什么
Billy, what are you doing.
你难道是在牲畜棚里长大的吗
You mother raise you in a barn.
别这样和我说话
Don't talk to me like that.
嘿 别生气
Hey, take it easy.
她的工作很累人
She's working hard.
谁给你气受了
What's eating you.
你 我妈
You.My Mom.
他
Him.
伙计
Buddy.
别闹了
Give it a rest.
Billy Billy
Billy.Billy.
我马上给你妈打电话
I'm gonna call your Mom.
让她来接你
Have her come and fetch you.
你敢
No, you are not.
跟我说一下具体情况
So tell me what's happening here.
我还指望你告诉我呢
I was hopping that you tell me.
是你先说起奇怪的现象
You are the one mentioned weird.
他们都从哪儿来
Now where did they all come from.
都是本地人
They are all locals.
四个最正常不过的普通人
Four of the straightest arrows you'd ever meet.
显然他们这样不是一天两天了
Apparently they've been acting like this for days.
他们的履历有什么共性吗
Do they share anyting in common.
去同一个教堂 学校 读书会什么的
Church, school, eh…bookclub.
据我所知 没有
Not in my knowledge.
我见过这孩子的女朋友
I met the kid's girlfriend.
她说他当时在搭便车
She said he was hitching a ride.
然后上了一辆小货车
When a van picked him up.
她就知道这些了
That's the last she's heard of him.
你看着办吧
Whatever that's worth.
你到底是什么 Billy
What are you Billy.
摆脱
Clear.
什么
Of.
一切
Everything.
这到底是为什么
Why are you doing this.
没为什么
You think there's a why.
没有 我就是想这么干
No.It's because I want to.
我可以这么干
And I can.
杂货店的监控资料
Grocery store surveillance pics.
好极了 谢谢
Great.Thank you.
喂
Hey.
怎么这么久才接
Well that took forever.
我在忙
Well, I'm working.
你有什么发现
You've got anything.
不好说 不过
Not sure, but.
又有好几个人开始发疯了
A handful of other people have started acting out, too.
什么样的发疯
Acting out how.
和那个女人一样
Well same as the woman.
特别暴力 有攻击性 易冲动
Agressive, violent and impulsive.
你进了健身房了吧
Sounds like you're in a gold's gym.
不过更少类固醇 更像是本性如此
Except it's less steroid induced, more basic instinct.
鸡毛蒜皮的小事就能把他们点着
It's like little things can set them off.
就像我那时候
Kinda like me.
你这个没人性的
You've got no instinct.
你真是病得不轻
I mean you are seriously messed up.
像你
You.
没有灵魂的时候 还记得吗
Yeah, souless me.Remember that.
当然 我怎么忘得了
Yeah, how can I forget.
但不像这些人 你没有彻底失控
But you weren't out of control like these people.
说的是没错
Yeah, well.
也许不同的人丢了魂儿
Maybe everyone has different reactions.
反应也不一样
When they are losing their soul.
有可能
Possible.
难道
So…what.
是十字路口恶魔
A crossroads demon making deals.
提前收账来了
And taking people' souls.
应该不是
No, I don't think so.
这些疯子也没人之前中过大乐透啊
I mean it's not as if there people are winning a lotto.
好吧
Okay.
那我就不知道了
Well that's my best swing.
别这样 Dean
I hope not, Dean.
我真的希望你来帮我一把
I can really use your help down here.
Dean
Dean.
怎么了 我在这
Yeah, I…I heard you.
我只是
I just.
我快找到了 Sam
I'm getting close, Sam.
我不能现在就放弃抓Abaddon的大好机会
I can't drop the ball on Abaddon right now.
好吧 小心些
All right.Be safe.
你跟Sam扯谎的时候 就像背着老婆在外偷情的丈夫
You are lying to Sam like he's your wife.
搞得我成了你的小三
Which kind of makes me your mistress.
听我说 年轻人
Now listen to me young man.
那些恶魔们回来了
Those demons are back.
相信我
I'm telling you.
往事重演了
It's happening all over again.
恶魔
Demons.
对啊 恶魔
Yes, demons.
你聋了吗
Are you deaf.
好的夫人
Yes, Ma'am.
我们马上着手处理恶魔事件
We are going to take care of those demons right away.
需要送您回去吗
Now do you want a ride home or something.
别忽悠我 你这个小混蛋
Don't patronize me you little turd.
这样吧 这事交给我吧
You know what I can take it from here.
我是Leiter探员
Agent Leiter.
请
Please.
给
Here you are.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
Sure.
要不您
Now why don't you.
跟我讲讲这些恶魔的事
Tell me all there demons.
Wilkinson女士
Mrs. Wilkinson.
请叫我Julia
Please.Call me Julia.
事情很简单 探员
It's very simple, agent.
他们
They.
他们以前来过米尔顿市
They came to Milton.
之后呢
And.
我说恶魔的时候 你眼睛都不眨一下
I say demons and you don't bat an eye.
而这里的其他人都觉得我一定是老年痴呆了
When everyone else around here thinks I'm nuts on toast.
或许我比其他人思路更开阔
Maybe I'm just a bit more open-minded than most.
也许吧
Maybe.
你跟他们是一类人 对吧
You are one of them, aren't you.
抱歉 他们是指
Sorry, one of who.
学者
Men of Letters.
他们在1958年来过米尔顿市
They came here in 1958.
学者们 来这儿吗
Men of Letters…came here.
是的
Oh yes.
那时候一切都不一样
It was different, then.
我也变了
I was different.
他们真是可爱的一对
They were a lovely couple.
Julia修女
Sister Julia.
请开一下门
Please answer the door.
好的 院长
Yes, Mother Superior.
晚上好 修女
Good evening, sisiter.
我们是宗教裁判所的
We are here from the Office of Inquisition.
你到底想干什么
What do you want.
我还想问你呢 Romeo
You tell me Romeo.
是你打电话叫我来的
You rang.
我猜猜
Let me guess.
是你手机自动拨了我的号码
You butt-dialed me.
随你怎么说
Whatever the hell that is.
不论如何 你废话完了没有
Either way, we done here.
事实上 既然我来了 上次我们聊天的时候
Actually, long as I'm here, last time we chitchatted.
我们一致同意 由你去找那个红毛小鬼
We agreed you were gonna line up Carrot Top.
是啊没错 我正在查
Yeah, well…I'm on it.
除非Abaddon爱逛小酒馆
Unless Abaddon likes ten cent wings.
吃廉价啤酒炸鸡
Stale beer and the clap.
我猜你在这儿是找不到她的
I doubt that she's here.
滚回地狱去吧
Go to hell.
我倒是想
If only.
你怎么回事
What's wrong with you, huh.
你把我叫出来 又想甩掉我
You call me, you hang up.
你想找Abaddon 又躲着她
You want Abaddon.You don't want Abaddon.
一会儿想要初刃 一会儿又不想
You want the Blade.You don't want the Blade.
要不是认识这么久了 我会怀疑你在拖延时间
If I didn't know you any better, I'd say you're stalling.
跟我说实话 我不告诉别人 你用初刃
Just between us girls, how did you feel.
削掉Magnus脑袋的时候是什么感觉
When you sunk the First Blade into Magnus' head.
没有砍你脑袋来得爽
Not half as good as I'm gonna feel when it's yours.
你拐弯抹角骂人的样子最可爱了
Love it when you talk it dirty.
要我说
You know what I think.
你一定觉得自己瞬间变强
I think you felt powerful.
阳刚之气暴增
Virile.
同时内心滋生恐惧
And afraid.
恐惧吗
Afraid.
别在诈骗大师面前班门弄斧 亲爱的
Don't scam a scam artist, darling.
你拖时间
You are stalling.
是因为你怕了
Cause you are scared.
他们用的是假名字 但是
They gave false names but.
不久后我知道了那个男人叫Henry
Later I learned that the man's name was Henry.
是Henry Winchester吗
Henry Winchester.
我不清楚他的姓
Never got last name.
好吧 那个女人呢
Okay, and the woman.
Josie
Josie.
你认识他们吗
Did you know them.
是的
Yes.
嗯 算是吧 这有点难解释
Eh, sort of, it's complicated.
我以前可是个修女 亲爱的
I'm an ex-nun, sweetie.
解释不清简直就是我的名字了
Complicated is my middle name.
那他们来是为了调查什么
Now, what were they here to investigate.
为了Mary Catherine修女
Sister Mary Catherine.
她杀了两个人然后从钟楼下跳下去了
She killed two people before jumping from the bell tower.
所以我带他们去见了修道院院长
So I took them to see Mother Superior.
还有Agnes修女
And sister Agnes.
时间紧迫 院长
Time is of the essence, Mother…Superior.
主教明早第一件事就是要见神父
The Cardinal's meeting with the holy father first thing in the morning.
他想要这件事情的报告
And he wants a report.
我们仁爱的修道院欢迎你们的神父
Our beloved abbey opened to your father.
Julia修女会是你们的向导
Sister Julia here will be your guide.
你们想从哪里开始
Where would you like to begin.
请带我们去Mary Catherine修女的睡房吧
Sister Mary Catherine sleeping quarters, please.
就从Mary Catherine修女的房间开始吧
Sister Mary Catherine's room it is.
我讨厌修女
I hate nuns.
为什么 就因为她回答了我 而不回答你
Why, because she answered me and not you.
不 因为我上的是天主教学校
No, because I went to Catholic school.
所以我积怨已久了
And I have a lot of pent-up-anger.
现在可不是诉苦的时候
No time for such pettiness.
你这么紧张兮兮的是怎么回事
What got all your boxers in such a bundle.
因为这个 为什么我们要在这儿
This, why are we out in the field.
这叫做边干边学
This called learning on the job.
而且你明明知道
And you know damn well this is.
这是我们成为正式成员前的最后一个任务了
The last assignment before we are full members.
这就是问题所在
There lies the problem.
离我们正式入会的日期越来越近
As our initiation grows closer.
我很担心这次行动会变成一次自私的莽撞之举
I worry this might be a selfish endeavor on my part.
自私 怎么说
Selfish, how.
如果我真的出了什么事
If anything would happen to me.
John和Millie怎么办
What about John, Millie.
他们会为你接受使命而感到骄傲
They will be proud to know you answered the call.
不 我妻子会变成寡妇 儿子也会失去父亲
No, my wife will be a widow and my son fatherless.
我不期望你能明白
I don't expect you to understand.
你根本就没有家
You don't have a fam.
对不起 Josie 我不是有意这样说的
I'm sorry, Josie, I didn't mean it that way.
我知道 Henry
I know Henry.
你是个好人 Millie和你在一起很幸运
You're a good man, Millie is lucky to have you.
就是这里
Here we are.
这些血迹怎么也洗不掉
The…blood wouldn't come off.
可以肯定这是一起恶魔附身事件了
So we are assuming demonic possession here.
对不对
Correct.
或者是一个语言学家突然发疯了
Or a linguist gone mad.
看起来很古老了 萨博拉语还是梵语
Looks ancients, Zapoqra or Sanscrit.
不 看起来像是古天使语
No, it is pre-Enochian.
是一种饰章
A crest of some sort.
地域骑士
Knights of hell.
那是什么
What is that.
大麻烦
Trouble.
地狱骑士 他们在那里做什么
Knights of hell, what were they doing there.
我对于那晚看到的所有事情都不敢相信
I'm not sure of anything I saw that night.
院长禁止我们
I couldn't leave our room after ten,
在10点之后离开卧房
Mother Superior forbade it.
别乱动
Stay still.
我在一个黑暗的地方醒来
I woke up in a dark place.
被绑在椅子上
Tied to a chair.
我不是一个人
There were others.
他们都被抓来了
They were taken.
我非常害怕 不停的祷告
I'm so scared, I prayed and prayed.
但是上帝没有回应我的祈祷
But god didn't answer my prayers.
是Henry和Josie救了我
Henry and Josie did.
[咒语]
你们这些猎人
Your hunters are always sticking your noses i.
总是爱多管闲事儿
In where they don't belong.
猎人 拜托 我们不是猎人
Hunters?Please.
那你们是什么人
Then what are you.
快说 否则他会为你的顽固付出代价
Quickly before this one pays for your stubbornness.
我们是这个世界的旁观者
We are perceptors, beholders.
记录一切超自然现象的人
Chroniclers of all that which man does not understand.
你居然是一个女学者
A woman amongst the Men of Letters.
是的
Yes.
这可真是个惊喜啊
Well, ain't that a blust.
你应该知道我们的能耐 恶魔
You do know we are capable of, demon.
是的 我知道你们自以为能对付什么
Yes, I know what you think you are capable of.
或者我应该自己去看看
Perhaps I should see for myself.
等等 你要干什么
Wait, what are you doing.
我要把这把老骨头换成这个梦幻小帅哥
I'm trading up from this bag of bones to Mr.dreamy here.
然后我就能零距离的研究你们了
Then I can study you kind real close.
不要 否则
Don't, or.
否则什么
Or what.
冲我来
Take me.
放过他
Not him.
别开玩笑了
You are joking.
我对你来说更有用处
I could be more useful to you.
人们总是低估女人的能力
People underestimated women.
不对
No.
这不是原因
That's not it.
你爱他
You love him.
知道吗 他也爱你
He loves too, you know.
把你当做妹妹
Like a sister.
求你了
Please.
放了他
Spare him.
冲我来吧
Take me.
我准许你进入我的身体
You have my permission.
你真把我逗乐了 亲爱的
You've been very entertaining, my dear.
我不需要你答应我
But I don't need your permission.
Abaddon要什么有什么
Abaddon takes what she wants.
现在 她想要一切
And right now, she wants everything.
你要研究那群学者了吗
You're going to study the Men of Letters.
等会儿
For a moment.
然后我就杀了他们
And then I'll destroy them.
这些烂摊子怎么办
And what of all this.
我回来之前继续演下去
Keep it going until I return.
装你的死吧
Now play dead.
Henry
Henry.
你没事吧
You okay.
我们成功了
We did it.
我们制止了恶魔
We stop the demons.
Abaddon
Abaddon.
你有没有看到 她具体在干什么
Did you ever see exactly what she was doing down there.
没有
No.
不管她曾经在圣博纳文图尔做了些什么
But whatever it was she was doing in Saint Bonaventure.
好像又开始了
It seems to be happening again.
那个修道院的名字是圣博纳文图尔吗
The convent's name is Saint Bonaventure.
是的
Yes.
在哪里
Where is it.
在郊区
On the outskirts of town.
那地方已经废弃很多年了
It's been closed for years.
我爱死这儿了 真的
I love this, I really do.
啤酒 自动点唱机
Couple of cold ones, a kind jukebox.
不管好坏 大家一起玩儿
Good and evil, bro-in down.
闭嘴Crowley
Shut your piehole Crowley.
你早就说过了
Yeah you said that already.
我只是暗示 你是有一点害怕了
Look, I merely suggested you might be a bit scared.
是吗 我可是第一次听你这么说
Yeah, No, I heard you the first time, you still don't know.
你自己都不知道你在说什么
What the hell you're talking about.
我知道Cain给了你他的印记是有原因的
I know the Cain gave you his mark for a reason.
我还知道你 从来没有接受印记
And I know that rather than embracing it.
从来没有当这是个礼物
Rather than looking at it as a gift that it is.
反而像丢了你的玩具一样
You're sulking like you lost your knuffle bunny.
你为什么在抗拒你的本性
Why are you fighting what you really are.
我是个猎人
I'm a hunter.
身上带有该隐之印的猎人
Who's the chip of the old Mark of Cain.
不 我猎杀都是有理由的
No.When I kill, I kill for a reason.
我跟Cain不是一路人
I'm nothing like Cain.
不是一路
Nothing like.
你在跟我说话吗
Who are you talking to.
我知道一定不是我
I know you are not talking to me.
去死
Well, eat me.
我都看到了 我看到你真实的样子了
I saw you!I saw the true of you together.
不像他 你喝的什么玩意儿
Nothing like him?What's in that bottle.
致幻剂吗
Delusion.
我开始担心你了 Dean
I'm starting to worry about you Dean.
是吗 你还是担心担心你自己吧
Yeah well, why don't you worry about yourself.
我很担心
I will.
不管你乐不乐意 我们都是一条绳上的蚂蚱
Cause like it or not, we are in this together.
你的麻烦就是我的麻烦 我们的麻烦
Your problems, my problems, our problems.
你要去哪儿
Where are you going now.
我去浇个花
I'm going to go water the lily.
想一起吗
Care to cross the streams.
很认真的哦
So serious.
下一次 会轻松很多
Next time, it'll be easier.
就这样
That's it.
很好
Good.
你会习惯这种感觉的
You'll get used to those feelings.
甚至会享受
Even welcome them.
慢着 我知道你想干什么
Easy, I know what you're thinking.
我只是想去洗手间 别挡道
I'm thinking I'd like to take a leave, so move.
我是Dean Winchester
I'm Dean Winchester.
我一眼就能认出来谁是猎人
And I know a hunter when I see one.
你不会想做你要做的这事的
You don't want to do what you're about to do.
为什么
Why is that.
因为你拿着把小刀就去和恶魔决斗
Because you're packing a knife to a demon fight.
你这是自寻死路
And you don't stand a chance.
那我也能死得光荣
Then I'll go down swinging.
听我说
Hey, listen to me.
如果不是情况特殊 我很愿意加入你
Any other day I knew I'd be right there with you.
哥们儿 相信我
Brother I would, OK.
但这回一定要听我的
But you gotta trust me in this one.
有种你就跟我来
Well you can grow a pair, and come with.
你以前猎杀过恶魔吗
You've ever taken on a demon before.
这就是了吧
Yeah.
最好相信我说的
Well trust me when I say it.
等他把你干掉
When he's done with you.
他回去追杀你的家人
He's gonna go after your family.
追杀你的朋友
He's gonna go after your friends.
甚至是你毕业晚会的舞伴
Hell he'll go after your prom date.
所以如果你真的想这么做
So if you wanna do that.
如果你想失去每一个你爱过的人
If you wanna damn anyone than anywhere you've ever loved.
你可能有一个非常渺茫的机会可以打赢他
Then a slightest chance you can win it by all means, pal.
你就去作死吧
You go right ahead.
我妹妹还很小
I got a kid sister.
她不该承受这些
She don't deserve that.
你叫什么
What's your name.
Jake
Jake.
很高兴认识你 Jake
Good to meet you, Jake.
谢谢
Thanks.
回头见
I'll see you around.
快点 我们该走了
Come on, we gotta go.
圣博纳文图尔修道院
St Bonaventure Convent.
恶魔根本不需要解决生理需求的好不好
I thought demons don't take leaks.
下次你想去找人吸血的时候
Next time when you want to shoot up.
找个好点的理由吧
Why don't you find a better excuse.
被你识破了
Guilty is charged.
怎么回事 我以为你会想办法摆脱掉这个麻烦
What happened?I thought you're cleaning up your act.
我本来是这么打算的
Well I was going to.
不过我做了个小小的自省
But then after a very little soul searching.
我决定正面我的人血依赖症
I decided to embrace my addiction.
你呢
What about you.
瘾君子最了解瘾君子
Takes a junkie to know a junkie.
你只是想再摸摸那个宝贝不是吗
You just want to touch that precios again, don't you.
我想杀掉Abaddon
I wanna kill Abaddon.
这就是我想做的
That's what I want.
不管初刃怎样了
So whatever happened to that blade.
都不用我来担心
I can't worry about that.
好吧 你就自我安慰吧
Sure.Whatever you could tell yourself.
这样你晚上就能睡个好觉了
So you can sleep better at night.
我想要什么 我害怕什么
But what I want, what I fear.
这些都不重要
None of that means squat.
因为这是我们杀死Abaddon
Because this is the one chance.
唯一的机会
That we have to kill Abaddon.
我豁出去了
So I'm all in.
不管后果如何
No matter what the consequence is.
所以我们还是照原计划进行
So the plan remains the same.
我找到她 你把初刃带来
I find her, you bring the blade.
我们的约会
It's a date.
有那么一刹那 我以为他要识破我了
For a second there I thought he made me.
他心思不在这上面
He has other things on his mind.
但是他的确像你说的那样
But he did do exactly what you said he would.
救了你
He saved you.
他当然会救我
Of course he'd save me.
我们是好闺蜜啊
The besties.
现在他终于准备好了
And now, he's ready.
灵魂是非常宝贵又脆弱的东西
Souls are very precious and fragile thing.
只要打碎了罐子
Break one of those.
灵魂就会立刻飞回原主人身体里
And then the little buggers fly right back home.
我们可不希望看到这样的画面呢 是不是
We can't have that now, can we.
这么多年之后
So after all these years.
你还是在帮Abaddon干这种卑鄙的勾当啊
You're still doing Abaddon's dirty works, huh.
Agnes
Agnes.
你相不相信其实更卑鄙了
Would you believe it's gotten even dirtier.
以前那么多的人都信上帝
Used to be folks believed in a church.
呵呵
Heck.
瞧瞧他们徘徊在这里追寻上帝的可笑样子
The way they come strolling in here looking for God.
就跟瓮中捉鳖一般简单
It's like fishing in a barrel, really.
但是
But.
时代变了
Time's changed.
这事儿还得怪你们这群无耻之徒
You can blame your pervert for that.
现在我不得不跟一个快递员
Now I'm in some shotgun in some.
挤在臭哄哄的送货车里
Smelly van with a handyman.
骗一些路人甲上车 取走他们的魂儿
And tricking any half-wit I can lay my hands on.
但是这都值得
But it's worth it.
因为盗取灵魂很高尚吗
Because stealing souls is so noble.
盗取灵魂是赢家的手段
Stealing souls is winning.
赢什么
Winning what.
地狱王冠啊
Hell's crown, nimrod.
你觉得Abaddon
You think Abaddon's just gonna sit there.
会放任那群好吃懒做的恶魔
While all those panty wasted demons.
迟迟不肯决定阵营吗
Refuse to pick a side.
她想出了个计划
And so she made a plan.
如果不能说服他们妥协
If you can't convince'em.
就用强的
Make'em.
她把灵魂转化成了恶魔
She's turning souls into demons.
恶魔军团
Demon army.
强不可摧 只效忠于她一个人
Unbeatable, loyal only to her.
照这个速度下去
At this rate.
怎么也得等好几百万年才能凑齐人数吧
She only took a couple of millions years.
祝你们好运
Have fun with that.
你以为我是唯一一个在执行任务的吗
You think I'm the only doing this.
我们有无数的分支
We have factories spread throughout.
别担心 胜利近在咫尺
Worry not though, victory is nigh.
希望你能加入我们
And we like you to be on our team.
招新工作很简单
Recruitment is easy.
我只需要把你的灵魂从身体里剜出来
I just have to rip your soul out of your body.
[咒语]
反抗是徒劳的
Please.
[咒语]
呃 我能问你个问题吗
You know…uh, can I ask you something.
如果你想约我的话 那还真抱歉
If it's for a date I'm sorry.
我从不跟65岁以下的人约会
I never see anyone under 65.
少不了一番矫情
Too much drama.
说吧
Spit it out.
在亲眼目睹你做的事情后 我很疑惑
After witnessing what you did.
为什么你没有把Abaddon的事儿
Why didn't you warn Henry.
告诉Henry
About Abaddon.
我成为一个修女
I became a nun.
是为了施助于众生
Because I wanted to help people.
让世界变得更美好
Make a difference.
但从没有人告诉你
But they never prepare you.
在面对世间真正邪恶的时候
They never tell you how to act.
该怎么办才好
In the face of true evil.
谢谢你 修女
Thank you, sister.
为了所有人的安全着想
For the safety of all those involved, it's important.
我们最好对今晚发生的事情
That we keep what happened here today.
闭口不谈
Quiet.
当然
Of course.
不久之后 我就离开了教会
Soon after I left the order.
为什么
Why.
因为我感到羞愧
Because I was ashamed.
我背叛了自己的种族
I had betrayed our flock.
不论是上帝 还是我自己
God, myself.
这曾经是 也会一直是我最大的耻辱
It was and still is my greatest shame.
你现在的所作所为 拯救了生命
Well, what you've shared with me saved lives.
没有你的帮助 我一个人干不了这个
And I couldn't have done that without you.
保重
Take care.
你也是 Sam
You too, Sam.
你还好吗 Henry
You okay, Henry.
好多了
Better.
今天我们救了那么多人
We saved lives today.
我们坚持的事业有了成效
We made a difference.
这个 我们的事业
This, our work.
是无比高尚崇高的 对不对
It's a noble calling, isn't it.
没错 这样做有一定的风险 但是天呐
And yes, there's risk, but Gosh.
这绝对是份高尚的事业
I feel the fool for doubting it for even a second.
你呢 Josie
And you?Josie.
我吗
Me.
我觉得整个人都焕然一新了
Well, I feel like a whole new person.
还在查资料吗
Still plugging away.
必须的 就像狗和骨头的关系一样
Like a dog with a bone.
你呢
You.
你是对的
You were right.
关于什么
About what.
尽快找到Abaddon
Finding Abaddon ASAP.
她正在收割灵魂
She's mining souls.
为什么
Why.
制造恶魔军团
To create an army.